tellyoubest.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - tellyoubest.com -- tellyoubest.com

* * *

## Legal Notice

We respect our user's privacy and make every effort to protect the privacy of the visitors to [Tellyoubest.com](http://www.tellyoubest.com/).

## 1\. Site Information & Contact

This website is owned and operated by Tellyoubest, Inc. The administrator for this site can be reached via email at tellyoubest@gmail.com. All efforts will be made to respond to any e-mail inquires within 48 hours. 

## 2\. Information that is collected

Information such as domain name, browser type and statistics for pages and deals that are being viewed are collected by this website. Tellyoubest only uses this information internally to improve the user experience of this site. Information such as e-mail addresses, contact information, comments etc. which is volunteered by visitors is also collected.

## 3\. No use by Children

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. Tellyoubest.com’s services are not written, intended, or designed for children under the age of 13. We do not collect personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13.

## 4\. Links to other websites

Tellyoubest links to several external sites such as merchants, advertisers, partners and sponsors. When leaving Tellyoubest to browse other sites, make sure you will review the privacy policy of those sites as it have some difference with Tellyoubest.com’s privacy policy. Tellyoubest is not responsible for the privacy policies of any third party web sites and this privacy policy statement does not apply to those Web sites. Tellyoubest makes no representation to the accuracy or existence of other websites' privacy policies.

## 5\. E-mail addresses

Tellyoubest only collects and stores names and e-mail addresses that are submitted voluntarily by our visitors. The e-mail addresses are used to send out newsletters and other related information and are never shared with outside parties except as detailed in section 9. Providing your e-mail address to Tellyoubest is voluntary and is not required to browse or use this site. If you have previously submitted your e-mail address to Tellyoubest but no longer wish to receive e-mails from us, please send an e-mail to tellyoubest@gmail.com and we will promptly remove your e-mail information.

## 6\. Financial Information

We do NOT collect any kind of financial information from our visitors. Any financial transaction you may enter into is strictly between yourself and the merchant you are purchasing goods or services from. [Tellyoubest.com](http://www.tellyoubest.com/) will not be responsible or otherwise liable for any use or disclosure of your financial information by such third parties. Please review the privacy policies of the merchants you are purchasing from for more information.

## 7\. Cookies

Tellyoubest does not make use of cookies. However, other merchants and organizations that are linked to on this website may set cookies when visiting their sites.

## 8\. Data Security

Tellyoubest takes reasonable precautions to keep all personal information secure. There are managerial and physical procedures in place to prevent unauthorized access to data. Please note that due to the open nature of the public Internet, you should consider any communication between yourself and [Tellyoubest.com](http://www.tellyoubest.com/) as non-confidential as we can not guarantee that all communication between you and our servers will be completely free from unauthorized access. The only personally identifiable data we store is though limited to names and email-addresses. No other personal data is stored.

## 9\. Sharing of Personally Identifiable Data

We do not divulge any information collected by us, or volunteered by our users, to any third parties unless; (i) We are required to do so by law, court order or subpoena; (ii) If required to enforce our Terms and Conditions; or (iii) If required to protect our website, trademarks and property.

## 10\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

Tellyoubest reserves the right to change and/or amend this privacy policy at any time with and without notice. Any updates will be posted on this page and are effective immediately.

## 11\. Your Acceptance

Your continued use of this site means that you understand this Privacy Policy and agree to its terms. Your continued use of this site also means that you understand and accept our Terms and Conditions.

## 12\. Questions and Suggestions

If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you can send an email at tellyoubest@gmail.com.

## 13\. Choice and Opt-Out

If you no longer wish to receive the our promotional communications, you may "opt-out" of receiving themby following the instructions included in each communication or by e-mailing at tellyoubest@gmail.com.
